luxehues.com 2015-09-19

# 

Radiant Hues CRM Solutions Pvt. Ltd ("Luxehues") is committed to ensure the privacy of its users (hereinafter referred to as "You" "Your" "Yourself") accessing its website located at www.luxehues.com ("Website") and has provided this Privacy Policy ("Policy") to familiarise You with the manner in which Luxehues collects, uses and discloses Your information collected through the Website.

**By using the website, you agree to the terms and conditions of this policy. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this policy, please do not proceed further to use this website.**

  * Information and Usage

This Privacy Policy explains how Luxehues collects personal and non-personal information, classified as mandatory or voluntary and uses, discloses and protects such information through the Website. 'Personal Information' is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a single person ("Personal Information"). Personal Information for the purposes of this Policy shall include, but not limited to, information regarding Your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, etc.

You may need to provide Luxehues Your Personal Information during the course of using some services of Luxehues, for instance, creating a User ID, provide information in Your account while registering on the Website, or provide financial information while making an online purchase, upload content, participate in any online survey or contest, communicate with Luxehues's customer service by phone, email or otherwise, provide reviews for the content available on the Website.

Luxehues collects only such Personal Information that Luxehues believes to be relevant and is required to understand you or your interests. In an effort to make our Website effective, certain information may be collected each time you visit the Website. Such information may be stored in server logs. These encrypted statistics do not identify you personally, but provide us the information regarding your visit to the Website and the type of user who is accessing our Website and certain browsing activities by You. This data may include: IP address of your server from where the Website is being accessed, the type of browser, the operating system of your system and the Website You last visited before visiting to our Website. The duration of your stay on our Website is also stored in the session along with the date and time of your access. These data are used by Luxehues to understand the use and number of users visiting the Website. Some of the information related to the Website and your visit to the Website may be shared by the sponsors, investors, advertisers, developer, strategic business partners of Luxehues and some associates in order to enhance and grow our business and the Website but we assure that this information will never include any of Your Personal Information. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major Websites.

When you use the Website, Luxehues 's servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically about your activities on the Website; for instance by way of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the Personal Information you submit to Luxehues.

Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the Website. You can also delete your browser cookies or disable them entirely, but this may significantly impact your experience with the Website and may make parts of the Website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on.

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the internet and sometimes on this Website. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Website, and Your interaction with our products and services. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. They do not know the name, phone number, address, email address, or any personally identifying information about the user.

Luxehues also uses the log file like other website servers which is the standard measures. They include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. We use them to analyse trends, administer the site, track a user's movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Luxehues does not share, trade or sell Your Personal Information in any manner, except as specified herein, or if express consent is sought from You.

Personal Information provided by you is used only:

    1. to facilitate Your use of the Website;
    2. to respond to your inquiries or fulfil your requests for information about the various services;
    3. to provide you with information about Luxehues's products/services and to send You information, materials, and offers from Luxehues;
    4. to send You important information regarding the Website, changes to Luxehues's terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information;
    5. to send You surveys and marketing communications that Luxehues believes may be of interest to You;
    6. to personalize Your experience on the Website and Luxehues's other websites by presenting advertising, products and offers tailored to You;
    7. to help you address your problems with the Website including addressing any technical problems;
    8. if you purchase any content or avail of any service from the Website, to complete and fulfil your purchase, for example, to have your payments processed, communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide You with related customer service;
    9. to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law.

You acknowledge that apart from Your Personal Information, if you upload any content on the Website, such content may contain information including Personal Information and the same may be available to the other users of the Website. Luxehues will not be liable for the disclosure and dissemination of such Personal Information to third parties.

Luxehues implements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception of Personal Information. However, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks.

  * Shared Personal Information

You are required to submit your information at the time of making an online purchase on the Website. Luxehues uses an online payment gateway that is operated by a third party and the information that you share with Luxehues is transferred and shared with such third party payment gateway operator. The said operator may also have access to your online purchase history/details that You make from the Website.

Extremely sensitive information like your credit-card details are transacted upon secure sites of approved payment gateways which are digitally under encryption, thereby providing the highest possible degree of care as per current technology.

  * Security

Luxehues strives to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of Your Personal Information and to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. For this purpose, Luxehues adopts internal reviews of the data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where Luxehues stores Your personal data.

Notwithstanding anything contained in this Policy or elsewhere, Luxehues shall not be held responsible for any loss, damage or misuse of Your Personal Information, if such loss, damage or misuse is attributable to a Force Majeure Event (as defined below).

A "Force Majeure Event" shall mean any event that is beyond the reasonable control of Luxehues and shall include, without limitation, sabotage, fire, flood, explosion, acts of God, civil commotion, strikes or industrial action of any kind, riots, insurrection, war, acts of government, computer hacking, unauthorised access to computer data and storage device, computer crashes, breach of security and encryption, etc.

  * Disclosure

Luxehues will use information only in accordance with the Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization.

Luxehues may disclose any information Luxehues may have about You (including your identity) if Luxehues determines that such disclosure is necessary in connection with any investigation or complaint regarding your use of the Website, or to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Luxehues's rights or property, or the rights or property of users of the Website, including Luxehues's customers. Luxehues reserves the right at all times to disclose any information that Luxehues deems necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request.

You acknowledge and agree that Luxehues may preserve any communication by You with Luxehues through the Website or any Service, and may also disclose such data if required to do so by law or if Luxehues determines that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (1) comply with legal process; (2) enforce this Policy; (3) respond to claims that any such data violates the rights of others; or (4) protect the rights, property or personal safety of Luxehues, its employees, users of, or visitors to, the Website, and the public.

  * User Discretion

You can always choose not to provide information and in such cases, if the information required is classified as mandatory, you will not be able to avail of that part of the Services, features or content.

You can add or update Your Personal Information on a regular basis. When you update information, Luxehues will keep a copy of the prior version for its records.

  * Miscellaneous

By accessing the Website, You have agreed to the terms set out in this Policy. This Policy should be at all times read along with the Terms of Use of the Website.

Unless stated otherwise, the Policy applies to all information that Luxehues has about You and Your account.

Luxehues may make changes to this Policy, from time to time at Luxehues's sole discretion or on account of changes in law. The revised Policy shall be made available on the Website. Your continued use of the Website, following changes to the Policy, will constitute Your acceptance of those changes.

If you choose to visit the Website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and the Website's Terms of Use. In addition to the foregoing, any disputes arising under this Policy shall be governed by the laws of India.

  * Grievances & Escalations

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer who can be contacted with respect to any complaints or concerns including those pertaining to breach of Luxehues’s Terms of Use, Term of Offer For Sale and other polices or questions are published as under:

Officer Name: Kapil R Singh

Email address: head.cs@luxehues.com

[09:30 AM to 6:00 PM from Monday to Friday except Public Holidays]
